<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE pkgmetadata SYSTEM "http://www.gentoo.org/dtd/metadata.dtd">
<pkgmetadata>
	<maintainer>
		<email>hasufell@posteo.de</email>
		<name>Julian Ospald</name>
	</maintainer>
	<longdescription lang="en">
		The Zod Engine is an open source remake of the 1996 game Z by the
		Bitmap Brothers written in C++ using the SDL library for
		Linux / Windows / Etc.

		The Story and Gameplay...
		In Z you were a commander under General Zod in his attempt to
		conquer the universe. Your team, Brad and Allan, went from site to
		site and planet to planet pushing back the Blue forces while getting
		bitched at by General Zod. In the Zod Engine the doors are opened
		up so that you can play all the levels and make new levels the way
		you've always wanted to. The Zod Engine is more then just a remake
		of Z however, it is a fully commercially supported online game that
		is perpetually running at all times. Players can connect and
		disconnect at any time.

		The Zod Engine is a MMORTS / RTS style game. In the game you command
		an army of robots and vehicles to take over neighboring territories
		in the ultimate goal of destroying all of your enemies. Unlike
		traditional RTS (Real Time Strategy) games the Zod Engine does not
		create units from collected resources but instead construction is
		constant from preset factories scattered throughout the level.

		What is New?
		The Zod Engine is a multiplayer oriented game where as Z is a single
		player oriented game. Here you will be able to for the first time do
		things such as play games against multiple bot players, or play the
		original levels with friends helping you on the same team. The Zod
		Engine is cross platform for Linux and Windows and can support any
		resolution. There are no limits on map size or players per game.
		The Zod Engine is also in a state of continual development so new
		features may come at any time with idea's from the players. 
	</longdescription>
</pkgmetadata>

